<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes"?>
<contentHaul xmlns:a="http://www.appian.com/ae/types/2009">
    <versionUuid>_a-0000e79b-0335-8000-9c0c-011c48011c48_2938324</versionUuid>
    <rule>
        <name>AS_FS_BL_AdditionalSystemAdminCenterIntegrations_v1_default</name>
        <uuid>_a-0000e6ca-7e19-8000-9bfb-011c48011c48_2226420</uuid>
        <description>This rule provides the configurations for each additional integration that is shown in the System Administration Center.


@customizable:1.0
@category:USER_INTERFACE
@app:FS</description>
        <parentUuid>_a-0000e4b1-2fbc-8000-9bc6-011c48011c48_968428</parentUuid>
        <visibility>
            <advertise>false</advertise>
            <hierarchy>true</hierarchy>
            <indexable>true</indexable>
            <quota>false</quota>
            <searchable>true</searchable>
            <system>false</system>
            <unlogged>false</unlogged>
        </visibility>
        <definition>/*

DESCRIPTION: This rule provides the configurations for custom integrations that are shown in the System Administration Center.


DEFAULT BEHAVIOR: 
There is nothing in here by default, but this list is merged with the objects in `AS_FS_BL_ootbSystemAdminCenterIntegrations`
which are shipped OOTB.


CUSTOMIZATION STEPS:
When adding a new integration to your application, add an instance of AS_FS_P_IntegrationSetting each here to view and configure
the integration in the System Administration Center.

The implementation in AS_FS_BL_ootbSystemAdminCenterIntegrations should be emulated closely.

Each Integration should have the following fields:
  integrationCode: This is the backend code associated with your integration.  It serves as the "primary key" corresponding to the integration.
  integrationLabel: This is the label attributed to your integration in the System Administration Center
  integrationIcon: This is the Appian icon attributed to your integration in the System Administration Center
  integrationUserImage: This is the image that will be displayed if the integration is referenced as a user in the application
    e.g. The Northrow integration generated an alert, and we show the Northrow user image in that context.
  integrationDescription: This is the text description of your integration shown in the System Administration Center
  isEnabledSettingCode: This is the code of the row in the AS_FS_ALL_USER_SETTINGS table that is used to determine whether the integration is active
  integrationMethods (optional): This list of methods is used for display purposes only in the System Administration Center
  apiVersion (optional): This text is used for display purposes only in the System Administration Center
  recordActionOverride (optional): By default, al custom integrations will use the "AS FS Integration Update Properties" process to update
    the integration status toggle and any other relevant settings provided in integrationSpecificSettings.
    If your integration has any more complex properties that need to be updated and do not fit neatly into the above process,
    make a custom record action and reference it here.
  testIntegrationAction (optional): We recommend building a process that can test the connectivity of the integration and referencing it here.
  additionalIntegrationProperties (optional): This is a rule reference to an interface containing a list of components that will appear in the
    third column of AS_EI_SCT_integrationDetails. This is how the third column of integration properties are added for the out of the box IDP 
    and Northrow integrations. This interface should only accept the following rule input:
      i18nData (anyType)
      readOnly (boolean)
      allUserSettings (list of AS_FS_AllUserSettings)
  additionalReadOnlyContents (optional): This is a rule reference to a read-only interface that will appear below the integration summary. 
    This is how the "Execution Details" section of the RPA integration is added to the summary page. This interface should only accept the following
    rule input:
      i18nData (anyType)
  
  
Note: Just adding methods or integrations in this rule will not automatically make them work in the app.
You must manually set them up in Appian and add them here to ensure that the System Administration Center can accurately display and update them.


PARAMETERS: 
None


EXPECTED RETURN TYPE: List of AS_FS_P_IntegrationSetting cdts

*/

{
  /*Add custom integrations here*/
  
  /*Sample custom integration template to follow: */
  
  /*'type!{urn:com:appian:types:AS:FS}AS_FS_P_IntegrationSetting'(*/
    /*integrationCode: "cons!MY_INTEGRATION_CODE",*/
        /*We strongly recommend using a constant for the integration code so you can refer to it elsewhere in the app*/
    /*integrationLabel: "My Integration",*/
    /*integrationIcon: "icon",*/
    /*integrationUserImage: cons!DOC_MY_INTEGRATION_USER_IMAGE,*/
    /*integrationDescription: "This is a new integration we are setting up",*/
    /*integrationMethods: {"Get Foo", "Post Bar"},*/
    /*apiVersion: "1.0.0",*/
    /*isEnabledSettingCode: "cons!MY_INTEGRATION_TOGGLE",*/
        /*We strongly recommend using a constant for the toggle so you can refer to it elsewhere in the app*/
    /*recordActionOverride: recordType!MyIntegration.actions.setProperties,*/
    /*testIntegrationAction: recordType!MyIntegration.actions.testIntegration,*/
    /*additionalIntegrationProperties: rule!MyCustomSpecificSettingsInterface,*/
    /*additionalReadOnlyContents: rule!MyCustomOtherComponentsInterface,*/
  /*)*/
}</definition>
        <namedTypedValue>
            <name>i18nData</name>
            <type>
                <name>Variant</name>
                <namespace>http://www.appian.com/ae/types/2009</namespace>
            </type>
        </namedTypedValue>
        <preferredEditor>legacy</preferredEditor>
        <offlineEnabled>false</offlineEnabled>
    </rule>
    <roleMap public="true">
        <role inherit="true" allowForAll="false" name="readers">
            <users/>
            <groups/>
        </role>
        <role inherit="true" allowForAll="false" name="authors">
            <users/>
            <groups/>
        </role>
        <role inherit="true" allowForAll="false" name="administrators">
            <users/>
            <groups/>
        </role>
        <role inherit="false" allowForAll="false" name="denyReaders">
            <users/>
            <groups/>
        </role>
        <role inherit="false" allowForAll="false" name="denyAuthors">
            <users/>
            <groups/>
        </role>
        <role inherit="false" allowForAll="false" name="denyAdministrators">
            <users/>
            <groups/>
        </role>
    </roleMap>
    <typedValue>
        <type>
            <name>RuleTestConfig?list</name>
            <namespace>http://www.appian.com/ae/types/2009</namespace>
        </type>
        <value>
            <el>
                <a:name>Unnamed Test Case</a:name>
                <a:ruleInputTestConfigs>
                    <a:value xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:type="a:Expression">#"_a-0000e50d-bf1d-8000-9bcd-011c48011c48_975720"(null)</a:value>
                    <a:nameRef>i18nData</a:nameRef>
                    <a:id>1</a:id>
                </a:ruleInputTestConfigs>
                <a:assertions xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:nil="true"/>
            </el>
        </value>
    </typedValue>
    <history>
        <historyInfo versionUuid="_a-0000e6ca-7e19-8000-9bfb-011c48011c48_2246712"/>
        <historyInfo versionUuid="_a-0000e6ca-7e19-8000-9bfb-011c48011c48_2272762"/>
        <historyInfo versionUuid="_a-0000e6e2-62e5-8000-9bfe-011c48011c48_2363956"/>
        <historyInfo versionUuid="_a-0000e6e2-62e5-8000-9bfe-011c48011c48_2365897"/>
        <historyInfo versionUuid="_a-0000e6e2-62e5-8000-9bfe-011c48011c48_2366353"/>
        <historyInfo versionUuid="_a-0000e6e2-62e5-8000-9bfe-011c48011c48_2371856"/>
        <historyInfo versionUuid="_a-0000e6e2-62e5-8000-9bfe-011c48011c48_2373579"/>
        <historyInfo versionUuid="_a-0000e6e2-62e5-8000-9bfe-011c48011c48_2382383"/>
        <historyInfo versionUuid="_a-0000e77e-5277-8000-9c09-011c48011c48_2871924"/>
        <historyInfo versionUuid="_a-0000e79b-0335-8000-9c0c-011c48011c48_2938324"/>
    </history>
</contentHaul>
